I just want to send a word out to everybody who's out there trying to figure out what to do next, who may feel stuck, who may not feel like they can figure out how to flip their life into the way that they want it to flip.
But I'm going to just give you this little tidbit of advice.
I ain't never seen nobody change where they at, staying where they at.
It may mean you need to change your zip code.
It may mean you need to change your state.
It may mean you need to change your country.
It may just mean you need to change your current residence.
And be around some folks that you ain't never been around before.
Get unfamiliar.
But the point is, I ain't never seen nobody change where they at, where they at.
So, in Newton's third law, what does it say?
To every action, there's an equal and opposite reaction.
You want a drastic change? Make a drastic change.
Ba-dum-bum!